tinyjuke.co 2018-08-30

# Privacy Policy | TinyJuke

This Privacy Policy governs your use of this site, regardless of how you access it, and by using this site you consent to all uses described in this Privacy Policy.

Information may be collected from you in various ways when you use this site. We automatically receive certain types of information when you interact with our Web pages. This information includes your computer or digital device's IP address, access times, your browser type and language. We may also collect information about the type of operating system you use, your account activity, and accessed pages.

We use unique identifiers to measure usage and analyze trends, administer the site and collect information for its databases. For more information visit [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) and [AddThis Privacy Policy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy).

Third-party websites or services linked to this site are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites may collect personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. TinyJuke.co is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites and companies or what they do with your information. You should make sure their privacy policy is acceptable to you. You may opt-out of third-party advertising cookies through the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

We may also update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and consider your information accordance with the version that was in place when you submitted it.
